{
    "subject": "resource/Diana_Gurtskaya",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1978-07-02",
    "human_readable": "Diana Gurtskaya was born on July 2, 1978.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9216523766517639,
            "question": "When was Diana Gurtskaya born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8099397420883179,
            "question": "What is Diana Gurtskaya's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7449959516525269,
            "question": "What month and day was Diana Gurtskaya's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5834471583366394,
            "question": "Diana Gurtskaya's birthday falls in which season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5463443398475647,
            "question": "Is Diana Gurtskaya a young adult?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.537679135799408,
            "question": "In what year did Diana Gurtskaya come into this world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5325866937637329,
            "question": "Is Diana Gurtskaya older than 45 years old?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4547535181045532,
            "question": "Has Diana Gurtskaya lived through three decades?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4487054646015167,
            "question": "How old was Diana Gurtskaya in the year 2000?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2880849838256836,
            "question": "Calculate Diana Gurtskaya's age in the year 2023."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Diana Gurtskaya was born on July 2, 1978.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1964_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old was Diana Gurtskaya in the year 2000?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1964_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Diana Gurtskaya lived through three decades?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1964_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Diana Gurtskaya older than 45 years old?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1964_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1964_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1964_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1964_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1964_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1964_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1964_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1964_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1964_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1964_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1964_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently provide information that supports the statement \"Diana Gurtskaya was born on July 2, 1978.\" This date is explicitly mentioned in multiple text snippets provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}